将切实帮助我们评估自己的表现
what they think we did right and wrong,
所以  要是你不介意谈的话...
so if you don't mind talking...
我觉得我不该这么做
I don't think I'm supposed to.
没关系  只在审判过程中不能谈论
Oh, no, that's just during the trial.
在裁决之后  你有权说任何想说的话
You have the right to say anything you want after the verdict.
-这事还没完  -怎么了
- This isn't over. - What's now?
他们在外面找陪审员谈话
They're out talking to jurors.
他们想要翻案
They're going for a reversal.
或是径为判决
Or judgment notwithstanding.
-现在有点晚了  -我知道
- It's just kind of late. - I understand.
那我能要你的电话号码吗
Why don't I just take your number
然后明天打电话给你
and I'll call you tomorrow?
10分钟就够了
Ten minutes tops.
你不必和她谈的
You don't have to talk to her.
他拥有自己的权利  凯里
He's well within his rights, Cary.
我和他解释过了
I explained to him.
我知道  但你有解释过
Yes, but have you explained
他根本就不必和你进行交谈吗
that he don't have to talk to you at all?